I've tried, which are John the Jins.
Father, we just want to thank you, Lord, for
Minimum and New desire to serve the community.
Father, we pray at the blessing, for each and every one of the
hearts Lord, and I pray that so that as they serve the community, and they
honor you, the way that's the way the community would honor them.
Father, we just thank you for those that you could in leadership, and
Lord, we know that they're doing your work in that leadership.
We pray all of this in Jesus mighty name, Amen.
Amen.
I play, but you can just say that why, I don't know how to say
that it's over.
And to the root of that, I look for which it stands, one nation,
another guy, and an invisible, liberty and justice, sir.
Thank you John.
I pray.
Poor people give them some kind of personal advances, but,
I'm fine with this.
Most true proof.
Thank you.
Hi.
John, hi.
Parker.
Hi.
Six months from the September 3rd, 2024,
by the immediate motion to prove.
Second.
Four.
Five.
Seven.
Benjamin.
Number 25, dash.
Zero.
Two.
The Justin, that's made.
They miss you a carryover.
Two actual carryover.
And we have every thumbs.
Approved in fiscal year, 2324, but not used by 63024,
to stay in the fiscal year, 2425.
Deal.
Perfect.
So during the budget season, we ask people to encumber their large projects
that they're not going to finish by the end of the year, to encumber that.
So when it's encumbered, it says, if it's spent.
So when we do our carryover projection, we will, we will, we will,
we will be a little lower, because it says if it was already spent.
So that's, that's how I can be confident that I can raise the carryover.
And now allow them to spend, or you will allow them to spend.
So that's what this does.
This amendment in the one of the next week.
Most true proof.
Hi.
Let me know today's email,
IMU.
mortality rate is 1, 2 , 1 2 , 1 and5 dollars per dollar per year.
Uh, hopefully you'll have a packet, in your heritage packet.
This is a, for, for your several things.
Global Things. GIS Component, Geotechnical Drilling and Reporting Flood Plane Management, and
Surveying the Services Topographic Services and Aerial Imigery.
progress part, this action will be taken, and I believe we don't have to, Tyler, I believe
we can just go ahead and contract that out or get with our engineers.
When we get all of this information back, we will share that with Mades, and hopefully get
some industry and some economic stability and development going in progress part.
So for example, one of the things of this grant is we'll have Geotech done out there, so
we'll go in there, those real different holes around the area, and say, okay, for a concrete
foot floor here, you need this thick, such as such, like the Lancy, when they pour the floor
out there for building, they had to pay to have someone do this.
So the city went out, and we got a grant to have this all paid for, so hopefully the next industrial
customer that would come out there, we could say, hey, we had all this stuff done, and a good
thing about this is through the Oklahoma Department of Commerce, and it is no match,
night, we get it all.
So let's do the whole park that's not, but then I mean, yep, so that would be huge.
I mean, you know, Lancy is just, you know, I mean, a customer, but I mean, it helps our utilities
so everyone of this customer is making it out there, it's beneficial.
And this is out at the same place for the Lancy as I said.
Yes, yes.
Since this will be our information we can share with you, whoever we need to share with.
I'll make motion.
I'll second.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Now another new minute is the meeting with the residents of the Bush and the President of this agenda.
10 staff reports.
11.
Community announcements.
12.
This meeting will be continued from the Council of Labor to remain in the staff room, the purpose
of the executive session at the completion of the regular meeting.
Pretty many months in the council.